

Rosario, Santa Fe, Argentina

Age: 22

Nationality

Argentine, Italian



+54 0341 367 7742



LINKS



linkedin.com/in/emelymack



<u>Portfolio</u>



github.com/emelymack



emelymackdev@gmail.com



🖣 LANGUAGES

Spanish

English

Italian



HTML & CSS

JavaScript

React

TypeScript

REST APIs

Bootstrap

Git

NextJS

EMELY MACK

FRONT END DEVELOPER -CERTIFIED PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Bilingual Front End developer & Full Stack Development student with 2+ years of experience and a passion for crafting impactful and effective digital experiences. Equipped with a diverse and promising skill-set. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.



EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Jr. Front End Developer at Axyoma Global, Rosario **MARCH 2021 - PRESENT**

- · Effectively implement the front-end of diverse projects, utilizing a comprehensive skill set including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap and React.
- · Successfully craft visually appealing, responsive and functional user interfaces to allow visitors on any device to have a perfect user experience.
- · Proactively maintain, update and optimize diverse websites front-end, ensuring seamless functionality and responsiveness, both in HTML/CSS and WordPress based projects.
- · Collaborate in decision-making processes that shape the technological stacks and workflows for various projects.
- Conduct manual testing in most complex projects and create bug reports identifying issues to deliver high-quality solutions.

Private English Lessons, Freelance, Rosario 2019 - 2020

- · Developed lesson plans based on the students' experience, focusing on improving English language proficiency and fluency in speaking.
- · Monitored students' progress and provided constructive feedback to guide their language learning journey effectively.



EDUCATION

Front End Specialist at Digital House - Scholarship **MAY 2021 - DECEMBER 2023**

Full-stack Web Development carreer co-created by Digital House, Globant and Mercado Libre, with the aim to train young professional developers following the highest standards in the industry.

Certified as Professional Developer in Dec 2022.

Tertiary Degree in Literary & Technical-Scientific Translation in English at IES N° 28 "Olga Cossettini" MARCH 2019 - ON HOLD SINCE MAY 2021

Senior High School Diploma 2014 - 2018

Graduated with honors.



Rosario, Santa Fe, Argentina

Age: 22

Nationality

Argentine, Italian



+54 0341 367 7742



LINKS



linkedin.com/in/emelymack



Portfolio



github.com/emelymack



emelymackdev@gmail.com



LANGUAGES

Spanish

English

Italian



SKILLS

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

React

TypeScript

REST APIs

Bootstrap

Git

NextJS

EMELY MACK

FRONT END DEVELOPER -CERTIFIED PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPER



COURSES & CERTIFICATES

React.js Essential Training at LinkedIn Learning

Web Accessibility - Testing tools for websites at ANDIS & **NIC Argentina**

2022

Web Development at Mimo

2021

JavaScript desde cero at EducacionIT

2020

CSS Fundamentals at SoloLearn

2020

SQL Fundamentals at SoloLearn

2020

The Science of Well-Being at Coursera & Yale University

2020

Interpersonal Public Speaking Course at Asociación de **Graduados UTN**

2020



QUALITIES

- Knowledge in agile methodologies
- Fast learning abilities
- · Joy in working and interacting with other people
- · Very dedicated, responsible and detail-oriented
- · Good listener, excellent interpersonal skills
- · Natural leadership qualities
- Constant personal and professional development
- · Ability to learn from my own mistakes, always try to give my best